Hello friends, today we will
talk about a giant company in the insurance sector.
Friends, the name of the company is
ICICI Lombard. It is a very good company. It is an
ICICI group company. Some
time ago, if we touch upon almost all the sectors, let's come
back. Now, it has seen a downfall of about 15-20 percent.
I have been tracking it for the last four-five days.
Every day, it is around
7878, so there has been a delivery rise of about 2%. So, a
lot of companies. You
can see here that in this way, it is
adding to one of its support levels.
What kind of support level is this by placing
this number here. Secondly, you can see here that at
this time, the company can take support at about two hundred
days' exponential moving average. From here, it can
pull back again. It
is a very good company. The
company has a market cap of about 74 thousand crores.
Friends, I will go through
its entire complaint and its
balance sheet, etc., what are its results
and what is its work in which sector. So,
friends, if we look at it as of today's date,
So there is a delivery of about 2%, a
very excellent delivery in this and the
matter is being raised continuously in this, so I think
people are also picking up this, this will be a
great investment person, if
you want, you can look for an opportunity for investment in this, you
can activate some stock in it little by little,
never keep a broom, at this time about 15
workers were reading for a long time, if we
look at this, we can
also make it quickly, friend, yes, you
can see here, there is not a single share please,
hello, there is no share please, the
rest of it is results etc., whatever boring bad
people can check, in a while, if
we have its overview, then here we can see that
ICICI Lombard is a
very leading company in the general insurance sector
and is very excellent
and we can see between them, its
market cap is about 70 thousand crores, its current
price is running from 15, if we
look at Apple Cider Lockheed, then it is 1675 and 1212
Touching its upper and lower sides, the
stock is trading at 56.73. If we
look at the price, the dividend is 181.
We can talk about this in point five ways.
If we look at the turn-on capital employed, it is
very impressive. The
accused of 1969, it can be considered very strong. More than
20%. By evening, we will see that the
return on equity is very
impressive. It is against 21.75. There is a
lot of possibility of stock split for and bones etc.
Its pure Happy G
Resort 2.39 is a little clear. The
building updates of the printers are 48.1%. Now
we can give more parameters in the chart.
People pray for a great appointment in 21 years.
If you guys are half, then it has been
trending strongly in April
and is gaining a good influence. It has just missed
its support again by almost subscribing.
As we thought, it is almost
subscribing right now, so this means the
possibility of school is very high. Along with this,
you can understand that if
Subscribe,
you guys can see here that it was almost
written in a professional chart, so its
chart pattern also looks quite attractive,
in each step, in each step, one is
moving in a pattern, so you
can see here, we keep some other things,
SP government gives, so you guys will be able to see
how amazing the chart of Satpal is also at
this time, that is, stop train, if we
ever invest in any stock, then all we have to do is
see that the stock is
in an up trend, it is different, we never
ride a sinking ship, always look
for the train, if it is in an up trend, then
always put a back in it, we will
leave you with its nutrition, which company has
reduced the exam date so much,
and it has almost become free, the company is on time
and good means which
Ashes is a very good series, that is, we
can ask continuously and in that, you have seen
in which, it always comes that 8.31 is
reading on it, it is
not very suitable, something of 151, you can see, I was
drinking and further on the issue
In comparison, we also saw that HDFC Life Insurance Company was
trending towards 660 for a long time. Police suddenly broke
out and returned from 740 to 66.
Friends, due to the prostate,
insurance companies had to make a lot of
payments, that is why there is a
slight decrease in it, that is a great
reduction. ICICI General Insurance Company
works in the insurance sector, we provide personal insurance in the two-wheeler sector, along with
SBI companies, wide companies,
HDFC Life Insurance, SBI
Life Insurance and ICICI Lombard.
And if we check its other parameters,
here we will see that its
operating profit has
decreased a little compared to its almost contact explanation. If we look at the operating profit, then it was
something like 70-80 crores in 2001, which
means more
subscribe and
80338860
[music]
almost half the
net profit
at 94476,
very
subscribe, which
means from July 1, and subscribe,
separated from Aam Aadmi on Noida Capsule
Swarn.  Even if we check its profit
statement, the operating
profit is difficult here it is 2,000,
this has decreased operating profit and we can
text message the profit, net profit is less, please
subscribe
and if the profit
on the tab screen
then it is
approximately 300 per text 8 crore in September 2008,
very good result, see the boring, the boring
of the company is also
decreasing, you can check it here
and apart from this, if we
look at its share holding pattern, you will also
see here that in this quarter, approximately
40% reaction has been seen regarding this trick, what do its promoters say, if you want then one
and a half
[music]
subscribe,
so subscribe to this channel
so that in this video,
if you want, the company is excellent and has a
good market, happy bay, attractive
valuations, debt is not much, the
reserves on the company are good, enter, but if
we talk about promoter holding, then
here this company is seeing itself as a drop
back  That's why if you guys
want then you can study it once and consult your
financial advisor, the company is doing well in the year
and you can get good returns in the short term, it is
updating about 15 now,
so I do not expect that
in the coming time the
stock price can reach 1718 committee, so friends
if you like this video then please
like this video and subscribe to the channel,
thank you very much for
watching this video, have a nice day